# Jeffrey Schrock

38 Windmill Hill Rd. | West Groton, MA 01472 | (978) 551-7403 <u>rhythmmagi@gmail.com</u> |

# Jr. Web Developer

Detail-driven and solution-oriented Web Developer with experience in serving clients on an individual and corporate basis, as well as delivering functional, practical solutions to meet their needs. Demonstrated capacity in IT Engineering and Customer Service, with a focus on software modification, software development, systems management.

#### **Technical Skills:**

OS/software installations, hardware upgrade and replacement, virus removal, troubleshooting hardware/software, port forwarding, inbound sales, website support, business consulting, order returns, conflict resolution.

**Languages:** HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, Node.js, Python, MongoDB, AWS, Vue.js, Sass, GML

#### Certificates

The Web Developer Bootcamp - Udemy - Colt Steele

# Professional Experience

\_\_\_\_\_\_

# Freelance Computer Support Technician - Groton, MA

April 2017 to Present

The primary focus was informing customers on proper use and care of both hardware and software, as well as assisted with the selection of parts and assembly of personal computers, including setting up operating systems and various software installations.

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Build, repair and install computer systems
- Update and backup software programs
- Install home networks

#### **Deluxe Corporation – Groton, MA**

Sales/Customer Service Representative – *May 2015 to March 2017* 

The role of Customer Service Representative required multiple proficiencies and deliverables;

The primary focus was providing individualized support to inbound calls inquiring about product on a detail-specific level. Further expectations included software testing for the improvement of the department, performing in the capacity of on-call systems management, and assisting with inter-departmental rollouts and updates.

#### **Responsibilities:**

- Sales representative for inbound calls
- Assisted with multiple pilots to test new software and provided feedback on issues and enhancements
- Evaluated voice scripts and provided changes for the wording and tones to better customer experience
- Trained co-workers on pilot software and hardware
- Provided first level tech support; troubleshooting, updating, and hardware maintenance for co-workers
- Completed multiple customer service training courses

## The Vinyl Vault. - Littleton, MA

Store manager – *April 2014 to May 2015* 

The role of Store Manager required a strong proficiency in networking and sales; The primary focus was maintaining the store and creating improvements through research and networking. Worked with other small businesses in the area to promote The Vinyl Vault by cross promoting and creating rapport with the community.

## **Responsibilities:**

- Handled all online social media and sales aspects of the business
- Managed store organization and pricing of inventory online and in store
- Maintain store and organized financials

#### Education

#### **Middlesex Community College**

591 Springs Road, Bedford, MA 01730 • (781) 280-3200

**Enrolled**: 2010-2014 **Major:** Performing Arts **Concentration:** Music

Degree Level and Status: Associates, Complete